Finding Aid for the J. Warren Perry Collection of Photographs, circa 1910-1971
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- People, circa 1910-1971, I.; 1199 photographs
  - Marianne Schech as Gutrune, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-040)
  - Marianne Schech as Sieglinde, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-041)
  - George Schick, Assoc. conductor Chicago Symphony, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-042)
  - Drawing of Tito Schipa, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-043)
  - Thomas Schippers, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-044)
  - Thomas Schippers, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-045)
  - Heinrich Schlusnus, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Gerspach, A. (Neustadt a. d. Haardt, Germany) (Box 13, Item C13-046)
  - Newspaper clipping about Heinrich Schlusnus, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-047)
  - Heinrich Schlusnus as Wolfram, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sandau (Berlin, Germany) (Box 13, Item C13-048)
  - Paul Schoeffler as Baron Scarpia, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 13, Item C13-049)
  - Paul Schoeffler as Jochanaan, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 13, Item C13-050)
  - Paul Schoeffler as Hans Sachs, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-051)
  - Friedrich Schorr as Hans Sachs, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-052)
  - Elisabeth Schumann, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 13, Item C13-053)
  - Carl Schuricht, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-054)
  - Carl Schuricht, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-055)
  - Carl Schuricht, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-056)
  - Carl Schuricht, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-057)
  - Clipping about Carl Schuricht, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-058)
  - Elisabeth Schwarzkopf as Donna Elvira, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fayer (Vienna, Austria) (Box 13, Item C13-059)
  - Elisabeth Schwarzkopf as Alice Ford, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 13, Item C13-060)
  - Elisabeth Schwarzkopf as the Marschallin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 13, Item C13-061)
  - Elisabeth Schwarzkopf as Countess Almaviva, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 13, Item C13-062)
  - Elisabeth Schwarzkopf as Fiordiligi with Nan Merriman as Dorabella, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-063)
  - Elisabeth Schwarzkopf as Donna Elvira, 1952-1953, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 13, Item C13-064)
  - Elisabeth Schwarzkopf as Fiordiligi, 1955-1956, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 13, Item C13-065)
  - Elisabeth Schwarzkopf, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-066)
  - Elisabeth Schwarzkopf as Countess Almaviva, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 13, Item C13-067)
  - Elisabeth Schwarzkopf, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fayer (Vienna, Austria) (Box 13, Item C13-068)
  - Elisabeth Schwarzkopf as Countess Almaviva, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 13, Item C13-069)
  - Elisabeth Schwarzkopf as the Marschallin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fayer (Vienna, Austria) (Box 13, Item C13-070)
  - Elisabeth Schwarzkopf as the Marschallin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fayer (Vienna, Austria) (Box 13, Item C13-071)
  - Albert Schweitzer, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Anderson, Erica (Box 13, Item C13-072)
  - Norman Scott as Pimen in Boris Godunov, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 14, Item C14-001)
  - Norman Scott as Monterone in Rigoletto, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 14, Item C14-002)
  - Norman Scott as Raimondo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 14, Item C14-003)
  - Norman Scott as Abimelech in Samson and Dalila, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 14, Item C14-004)
  - Norman Scott as Colline, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 14, Item C14-005)
  - Antonio Scotti as Baron Scarpia, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-006)
  - Renata Scotto as Micaela with Giuseppe Di Stefano as Don Jose, 1960, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 14, Item C14-007)
  - Renata Scotto as Micaela, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 14, Item C14-008)
  - Irmgard Seefried, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fayer (Vienna, Austria) (Box 14, Item C14-009)
  - Irmgard Seefried, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Simonis (Vienna, Austria) (Box 14, Item C14-010)
  - Berl Senofsky, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-011)
  - Tullio Serafin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Publifoto (Box 14, Item C14-012)
  - Tullio Serafin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Salvini, Renato (Florence, Italy) (Box 14, Item C14-013)
  - Tullio Serafin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 14, Item C14-014)
  - Mario Sereni as Alfredo Germont, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-015)
  - Mario Sereni as Carlo Gerard, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 14, Item C14-016)
  - Rudolf Serkin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-017)
  - Rudolf Serkin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-018)
  - Ms. thank you note from Rudolf Serkin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-019)
  - Fabien Sevitsky, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-020)
  - Louis Sgarro, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 14, Item C14-021)
  - Louis Sgarro as King of Egypt in Aida, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 14, Item C14-022)
  - Robert Shaw, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-023)
  - Typescript thank you note from Robert Shaw, 1953 Oct. 28, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-024)
  - Robert Shaw, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-025)
  - Robert Shaw, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-026)
  - Robert Shaw, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-027)
  - Jean Sibelius, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Pietinen (Helsinki, Finland) (Box 14, Item C14-028)
  - Cesare Siepi as King Philippe II, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 14, Item C14-029)
  - Cesare Siepi as Boris Godunov, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 14, Item C14-030)
  - Cesare Siepi as Don Giovanni, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 14, Item C14-031)
  - Cesare Siepi as Don Giovanni, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 14, Item C14-032)
  - Cesare Siepi as King Philippe II, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-033)
  - Cesare Siepi as Figaro, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 14, Item C14-034)
  - Cesare Siepi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-035)
  - Cesare Siepi as Oroveso in Norma, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Villani (Box 14, Item C14-036)
  - Cesare Siepi as Don Giovanni, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 14, Item C14-037)
  - Cesare Siepi as Alvise Badoero, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 14, Item C14-038)
  - Cesare Siepi as Padre Guardiano, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 14, Item C14-039)
  - Paolo Silveri as Guillaume Tell, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Cantera (Rome, Italy) (Box 14, Item C14-040)
  - Paolo Silveri as Baron Scarpia, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 14, Item C14-041)
  - Paolo Silveri as Rodrigue in Don Carlos, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 14, Item C14-042)
  - Giulietta Simionato as Giovanna Seymour, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 14, Item C14-043)
  - Giulietta Simionato as Eboli, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-044)
  - Giulietta Simionato as Amneris, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 14, Item C14-045)
  - Giulietta Simionato in Handel's Giulio Cesare, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 14, Item C14-046)
  - Giulietta Simionato as Santuzza, 1954-1955, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 14, Item C14-047)
  - Giulietta Simionato as Mignon, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-048)
  - Giulietta Simionato as Cenerentola, 1953-1954, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 14, Item C14-049)
  - Giulietta Simionato as Adalgisa, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 14, Item C14-050)
  - Giulietta Simionato as Dalila, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 14, Item C14-051)
  - Giulietta Simionato as Amneris, 1960, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-052)
  - Giulietta Simionato as Azucena, 1959 Oct. 26, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 14, Item C14-053)
  - Giulietta Simionato as Aida with Mario Del Monaco as Radames and conductor Fausto Cleva, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Trifoto (Verona, Italy) (Box 14, Item C14-054)
  - Leopold Simoneau as Don Ottavio, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Toepffer, Sabine (Munich, Germany) (Box 14, Item C14-055)
  - Leopold Simoneau as Alfredo Germont, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 14, Item C14-056)
  - Martial Singher as Figaro, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-057)
  - Martial Singher as Iago, 1930s, 1 black and white photograph; Goursat (Paris, France) (Box 14, Item C14-058)
  - Martial Singher as Hamlet, 1930s, 1 black and white photograph; Granere (Paris, France) (Box 14, Item C14-059)
  - Martial Singher as Pelleas, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-060)
  - Martial Singher as Pelleas (painting by Wayman Adams), undated, 1 black and white photograph; Adams, Wayman, 1883-1959 (Box 14, Item C14-061)
  - Martial Singher as Count Almaviva, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Sudak, Teatro Colon (Box 14, Item C14-062)
  - Martial Singher as Mercutio, 1944-1945, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-063)
  - Martial Singher as Golaud, 1953-1954, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 14, Item C14-064)
  - Zadel Skolovsky, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bruno of Hollywood (New York, N.Y.) (Box 14, Item C14-065)
  - Jenska Slebos, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Chase, Merrill (Box 14, Item C14-066)
  - Pianist Solomon, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-067)
  - Georg Solti, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fayer (Vienna, Austria) (Box 14, Item C14-068)
  - Georg Solti, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 14, Item C14-069)
  - Ina Souez as Donna Anna, undated, 1 black and white photograph; De Bellis (New York, N.Y.) (Box 14, Item C14-070)
  - Albert Spalding, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-001)
  - Tossy Spivakovsky, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-002)
  - Sylvia Stahlman as Oscar, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 15, Item C15-003)
  - Eleanor Steber as the Marschallin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 15, Item C15-004)
  - Eleanor Steber as Tosca, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bender (Box 15, Item C15-005)
  - Eleanor Steber as Manon, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 15, Item C15-006)
  - Eleanor Steber as Fiordiligi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Halsman (New York, N.Y.) (Box 15, Item C15-007)
  - Eleanor Steber as Elsa, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 15, Item C15-008)
  - Eleanor Steber as Countess Almaviva, undated, 1 black and white photograph; De Bellis (New York, N.Y.) (Box 15, Item C15-009)
  - Eleanor Steber as Vanessa, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 15, Item C15-010)
  - Eleanor Steber as Elsa, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 15, Item C15-011)
  - Eleanor Steber, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-012)
  - Eleanor Steber as Tosca, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bender (Box 15, Item C15-013)
  - Eleanor Steber as the Marschallin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-014)
  - Eleanor Steber as Tosca with Barry Morrell as Cavaradossi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 15, Item C15-015)
  - Eleanor Steber as Donna Anna, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 15, Item C15-016)
  - Eleanor Steber as Arabella, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 15, Item C15-017)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marguerite, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-018)
  - Eleanor Steber as Donna Anna, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 15, Item C15-019)
  - Eleanor Steber as Marie in Wozzeck, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 15, Item C15-020)
  - William Steinberg, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Kastan, Erich (Box 15, Item C15-021)
  - William Steinberg, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-022)
  - William Steinberg, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-023)
  - Antonietta Stella as Violetta, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 15, Item C15-024)
  - Antonietta Stella as Tosca, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-025)
  - Antonietta Stella as Violetta, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Benzoliuti (Rome, Italy) (Box 15, Item C15-026)
  - Antonietta Stella as Aida, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lerner, Frank (Box 15, Item C15-027)
  - Antonietta Stella as Cio-Cio San, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 15, Item C15-028)
  - Antonietta Stella as Mimi, 1957, 1 black and white photograph; Irifoto (Box 15, Item C15-029)
  - Isaac Stern, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-030)
  - Isaac Stern clipping, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-031)
  - Isaac Stern, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-032)
  - Isaac Stern, undated, 1 black and white photograph; British Travel and Holidays Association (Box 15, Item C15-033)
  - RisÃ‹ Stevens as Octavian, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 1, Item C15-034)
  - RisÃ‹ Stevens as Carmen, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bender (Box 15, Item C15-035)
  - RisÃ‹ Stevens as Carmen, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bender (Box 15, Item C15-036)
  - RisÃ‹ Stevens as Orfeo, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bender (Box 15, Item C15-037)
  - RisÃ‹ Stevens as Carmen, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-038)
  - Teresa Stich-Randall in costume, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fayer (Vienna, Austria) (Box 15, Item C15-039)
  - Teresa Stich-Randall with dog, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-040)
  - Teresa Stich-Randall, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-041)
  - Fritz Stiedry, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 15, Item C15-042)
  - Ebe Stignani as Dalila, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Camuzzi, M (Box 15, Item C15-043)
  - Ebe Stignani as Adalgisa, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-044)
  - Ebe Stignani as Azucena, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 15, Item C15-045)
  - Ebe Stignani as Ulrica, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 15, Item C15-046)
  - Ebe Stignani, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-047)
  - Frederick Stock, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Fujita, Jun (Chicago, Ill.) (Box 15, Item C15-048)
  - Frederick Stock, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Atwell, H.A (Box 15, Item C15-049)
  - Frederick Stock, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Nelidoff, George (Chicago, Ill.) (Box 15, Item C15-050)
  - Frederick Stock with Arnold Schoenberg, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-051)
  - Leopold Stokowski, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bender (Box 15, Item C15-052)
  - Leopold Stokowski, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Bender (Box 15, Item C15-053)
  - Leopold Stokowski, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-054)
  - Leopold Stokowski, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Moss Photo (New York, N.Y.) (Box 15, Item C15-055)
  - Igor Stravinsky, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-056)
  - Igor Stravinsky, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-057)
  - Igor Stravinsky with George Balanchine, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-058)
  - Igor Stravinsky at piano, Nicola Malko conducting Copenhagen Orchestra, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-059)
  - Soulima Stravinsky, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-060)
  - Rita Streich as Susanna in Marriage of Figaro, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 15, Item C15-061)
  - Rita Streich as Zerbinetta, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Lackenbach, Robert (Box 15, Item C15-062)
  - Grete Stückgold, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mitchell, Herbert, (New York, N.Y.) (Box 15, Item C15-063)
  - Brian Sullivan as Lohengrin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 16, Item C16-001)
  - Brian Sullivan as Tamino, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 16, Item C16-002)
  - Brian Sullivan, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-003)
  - Yma Sumac as Lakme, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-004)
  - Marie Sundelius, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-005)
  - Joan Sutherland in costume, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-006)
  - Joan Sutherland as Donna Anna, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-007)
  - Joan Sutherland as Lucia, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-008)
  - Joan Sutherland as Amina, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-009)
  - Joan Sutherland as Lucia?, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-010)
  - Joan Sutherland as Rodelinda, 1959, 1 black and white photograph; Rogers, Houston (Box 16, Item C16-011)
  - Set Svanholm as Siegfried, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-012)
  - Set Svanholm as Tristan, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-013)
  - Set Svanholm as Tristan, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-014)
  - Set Svanholm as Lohengrin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-015)
  - Set Svanholm as Admetus, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 16, Item C16-016)
  - Set Svanholm as Siegfried, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-017)
  - Alexander Sved as Count di Luna, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Foto Sudak, Teatro Colon (Box 16, Item C16-018)
  - Gladys Swarthout as Carmen, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-019)
  - Typescript note from Gladys Swarthout, 1951 Sept. 11, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-020)
  - Gladys Swarthout as Carmen, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-021)
  - Gladys Swarthout, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-022)
  - Gladys Swarthout, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-023)
  - George Szell, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sherman, Editta (Box 16, Item C16-024)
  - George Szell, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Moss Photo (New York, N.Y.) (Box 16, Item C16-025)
  - George Szell, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-026)
  - George Szell, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Moss Photo (New York, N.Y.) (Box 16, Item C16-027)
  - Joseph Szigeti, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-028)
  - Joseph Szigeti, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-029)
  - Giuseppe Taddei as Iago, 1958, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-030)
  - Giuseppe Taddei as Papageno, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 16, Item C16-031)
  - Giuseppe Taddei as Carlo Gerard, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 16, Item C16-032)
  - Ferruccio Tagliavini, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 16, Item C16-033)
  - Ferruccio Tagliavini as Faust, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-034)
  - Ferruccio Tagliavini as Des Grieux, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 16, Item C16-035)
  - Ferruccio Tagliavini as Cavaradossi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 16, Item C16-036)
  - Ferruccio Tagliavini as Faust in Mefistofole, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 16, Item C16-037)
  - Ferruccio Tagliavini as Des Grieux, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 16, Item C16-038)
  - Ferruccio Tagliavini as Count Almaviva, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 16, Item C16-039)
  - Italo Tajo as Mephistopheles, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-040)
  - Pia Tassinari as Manon, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Abresch, James (Box 16, Item C16-041)
  - Alexander Tcherepnin, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Harcourt (Paris, France) (Box 16, Item C16-042)
  - Renata Tebaldi as Amelia Grimaldi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 16, Item C16-043)
  - Renata Tebaldi as Manon, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 16, Item C16-044)
  - Renata Tebaldi as Maddalena de Coigny, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-045)
  - Renata Tebaldi as Mimi, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 16, Item C16-046)
  - Renata Tebaldi as Tosca, undated, 1 black and white photograph; LeBlang, Sedge (Box 16, Item C16-047)
  - Renata Tebaldi as Adriana, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Sorensen, Nancy (Box 16, Item C16-048)
  - Renata Tebaldi as Violetta, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Mélançon, Louis (Box 16, Item C16-049)
  - Renata Tebaldi as Adriana, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Piccagliani, Erio (Box 16, Item C16-050)